Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1920 -- 1999; 1985 -- 1996; MS074.002; 38.4 Linear Feet
  - Christic Institute, 1985 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - Christmas, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Church Arson Task Force, 1996; MS074.002.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Church growth, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Church schools, 1985 -- 1986; MS074.002.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Church & state issues, 1984 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Church Universal & Triumphant CUT, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - Circle, 1986 -- 1989; MS074.002.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Circumcision, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Decency Through Law, 1986 -- 1989; MS074.002.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Decency Through Law Reporter, 1987 -- 1989; MS074.002.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Excellence, 1988 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Fair School Taxes, 1994; MS074.002.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Life, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Citizens for Proportional Representation, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Citizens Project, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Citizens United, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Civil Liberties, ACLU, 1992; MS074.002.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Civil Rights, 1987 -- 1991; MS074.002.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Claremont Institute, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00028 (Box 42)
  - Fred Clarkson, 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00029 (Box 42)
  - Clear TV, 1989; MS074.002.042.00030 (Box 42)
  - Clergy abuse, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00031 (Box 42)
  - Clergy & Laity Concerned, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00032 (Box 42)
  - Clergy & Laity United for America, 1994; MS074.002.042.00033 (Box 42)
  - Clergy malpractice, 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00034 (Box 42)
  - Clergy volunteer program, 1990; MS074.002.042.00035 (Box 42)
  - Clerkin, Donald V., 1989; MS074.002.042.00036 (Box 42)
  - Clinton and the religious right, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00037 (Box 42)
  - CLF Reporter, 1989; MS074.002.042.00038 (Box 42)
    CLF Reporter Published by Children's Legal Foundation
  - Clinton, Bill, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00039 (Box 42)
  - Clinton/Jewish groups, 1993; MS074.002.042.00040 (Box 42)
  - Clinton - religion, 1994; MS074.002.042.00041 (Box 42)
  - Coalition building, challenging the Christian right, 3rd edition, 1992; MS074.002.042.00042 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for Choice, 1993; MS074.002.042.00043 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for Reproductive Choice, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00044 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for Freedom of Expression, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00045 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for the Protection of American Values, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00046 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for Religious Freedom, 1982 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00047 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for Secular Humanism and Free Thought, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00048 (Box 42)
  - Coalition to Preserve Traditional Values, 1990; MS074.002.042.00049 (Box 42)
  - Coalition for the Protection of American Values (CPAV), 1993; MS074.002.042.00050 (Box 42)
  - COR Newsletter, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00051 (Box 42)
    COR = Coalition on Revival
  - COR Fact Sheet, 1993; MS074.002.042.00052 (Box 42)
  - COR Coalition on Revival, 1987 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00053 (Box 42)
  - Coalition on Revival [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00054 (Box 42)
  - Coalition on Revival [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00055 (Box 42)
  - Codesh, 1988 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00056 (Box 42)
  - Cohen, Edmund, 1987 -- 1997; MS074.002.042.00057 (Box 42)
  - Cohen, Rabbi H., 1995; MS074.002.042.00058 (Box 42)
  - Colorado, 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00059 (Box 42)
  - Colorado for Family Values, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00060 (Box 42)
  - Dave Collins - Lynchburg, 1987; MS074.002.042.00061 (Box 42)
  - Colorado Springs Christians, 1988 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00062 (Box 42)
  - Colorado - religious right, 1990 -- 1992; MS074.002.042.00063 (Box 42)
  - Colson, Charles, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00064 (Box 42)
  - Columbia Journalism Review, 1996; MS074.002.042.00065 (Box 42)
  - Columbia Journalism Review, 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00066 (Box 42)
  - Committee for a Constructive Tomorrow (CFACT), 1992; MS074.002.042.00067 (Box 42)
  - Committee to Save Public Media, MS074.002.042.00068 (Box 42)
  - Common Cause, 1988 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00069 (Box 42)
  - Common Ground Network for LIfe and Choice, 1995; MS074.002.042.00070 (Box 42)
  - Communism, 1987; MS074.002.042.00071 (Box 42)
  - Community Coalition Network, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00072 (Box 42)
  - Computers & religion, 1994; MS074.002.042.00073 (Box 42)
  - Conason, Joe, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00074 (Box 42)
  - Condoms, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00075 (Box 42)
  - Confederate flag, 1996; MS074.002.042.00076 (Box 42)
  - Congress, 1996; MS074.002.042.00077 (Box 42)
  - Connecticut, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.042.00078 (Box 42)
  - Conrad, Jane, 1993; MS074.002.042.00079 (Box 42)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1996; MS074.002.042.00080 (Box 42)
  - Conservative Digest, 1980 -- 1994; MS074.002.042.00081 (Box 42)
  - Conservatively Incorrect, 1995; MS074.002.042.00082 (Box 42)
  - Conservatives, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.042.00083 (Box 42)
  - Constitution (U.S.), 1985 -- 1995; MS074.002.042.00084 (Box 42)
  - Constitution - Bicentennial, 1985 -- 1987; MS074.002.042.00085 (Box 42)
  - Constitutional Legal Institute of New England, 1994; MS074.002.042.00086 (Box 42)
  - Constitutional Rights Foundation, 1995; MS074.002.042.00087 (Box 42)
  - Contact America, 1987; MS074.002.042.00088 (Box 42)
  - Representative Silvio O. Conte, 1990; MS074.002.042.00089 (Box 42)
  - Contract With America, 1995; MS074.002.042.00090 (Box 42)
  - Conversions, 1995; MS074.002.042.00091 (Box 42)
  - Contras, 1986 -- 1989; MS074.002.042.00092 (Box 42)
  - Cooperative Baptist Fellowship, 1996; MS074.002.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Coors, 1975 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - COPAC, 1996; MS074.002.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Cornerstone, MS074.002.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Albert H. Corliss, 1987; MS074.002.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Cornfield, Darlene, 1995; MS074.002.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence - misc., 1984 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - Council for Authentic Judaism, 1995; MS074.002.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Council for Democratic & Secular Humanism: Secular Humanist Bulletin, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - CNP-Council for National Policy, 1996; MS074.002.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - Council on Religious Freedom, 1992; MS074.002.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Courts, PH article, 1988; MS074.002.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Courts, rulings, miscellaneous, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Couser, Richard, 1994; MS074.002.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Covenant House, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Covert Action, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Cox, Harvey, theologian, 1995; MS074.002.043.00017 (Box 43)
  - Cozic, Charles, 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.043.00018 (Box 43)
  - CPAV - Coalition for the Protection of American Values, 1995; MS074.002.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - Crane, Capt. Steven, 1994; MS074.002.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - Creation science, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00021 (Box 43)
  - Creationism - general, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Creationism - interviews, Kors, 1996; MS074.002.043.00023 (Box 43)
  - Creation spirituality, 1989 -- 1990; MS074.002.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Creche cases, 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Crisis Pregnancy Centers, 1994; MS074.002.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - Crosses, 1989; MS074.002.043.00027 (Box 43)
  - Crossfire, 1985 -- 1986; MS074.002.043.00028 (Box 43)
  - Crowell, Rick, 1991; MS074.002.043.00029 (Box 43)
  - Crutcher, Mark, 1994; MS074.002.043.00030 (Box 43)
  - Cruel & unusual punishment, 1991; MS074.002.043.00031 (Box 43)
  - Cults - articles against, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00032 (Box 43)
  - Cults - misc., 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00033 (Box 43)
  - Culture Changers (Christians in Action), 1994; MS074.002.043.00034 (Box 43)
  - Culture wars, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00035 (Box 43)
  - CultWatch Response, 1988 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00036 (Box 43)
  - Cunningham, Greg, 1994; MS074.002.043.00037 (Box 43)
  - Cunningham, Joseph, 1992; MS074.002.043.00038 (Box 43)
  - Cunningham, Randy (Duke), 1992; MS074.002.043.00039 (Box 43)
  - Cuomo campaign, 1994; MS074.002.043.00040 (Box 43)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1984; MS074.002.043.00041 (Box 43)
  - Cuomo, Governor Mario, 1985; MS074.002.043.00042 (Box 43)
  - Current affair, a, 1991; MS074.002.043.00043 (Box 43)
  - Current Thoughts and Trends, 1992; MS074.002.043.00044 (Box 43)
  - Cyberporn, 1995; MS074.002.043.00045 (Box 43)
  - CWA convention, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.043.00046 (Box 43)
  - CWA fact sheet, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00047 (Box 43)
  - Concerned Women for America, 1989 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00048 (Box 43)
  - Concerned Women [1 of 3], 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00049 (Box 43)
  - Concerned Women [2 of 3], 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00050 (Box 43)
  - Concerned Women [3 of 3], 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00051 (Box 43)
  - Concerned Women for America of Mass., 1996; MS074.002.043.00052 (Box 43)
  - Dade, Malcolm, 1990; MS074.002.043.00053 (Box 43)
  - Dame, Reverend Calvin O., 1986; MS074.002.043.00054 (Box 43)
  - Dannemeyer, William, 1992; MS074.002.043.00055 (Box 43)
  - D'Antonio, Michael, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00056 (Box 43)
  - Dark Ages Weekend, 1995; MS074.002.043.00057 (Box 43)
  - Dart, John, 1984 -- 1988; MS074.002.043.00058 (Box 43)
  - Datacenter, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00059 (Box 43)
  - Davis, Robert Gorham, 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00060 (Box 43)
  - De Armond, Paul & Claire, 1994; MS074.002.043.00061 (Box 43)
  - Deacon Beacon, 1995; MS074.002.043.00062 (Box 43)
  - Dean, Mary F., 1995; MS074.002.043.00063 (Box 43)
  - Decter, Midge, 1995; MS074.002.043.00064 (Box 43)
  - Dedman, Bill, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.043.00065 (Box 43)
  - Dees, Morris, 1996; MS074.002.043.00066 (Box 43)
  - Defensive Action, 1994; MS074.002.043.00067 (Box 43)
  - Defensive Action petition, 1995; MS074.002.043.00068 (Box 43)
  - Dekker, Reverend John A., 1986 -- 1990; MS074.002.043.00069 (Box 43)
  - Delaware, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00070 (Box 43)
  - Delgaudio, Eugene A., 1992; MS074.002.043.00071 (Box 43)
  - Demar, Gary, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00072 (Box 43)
  - Democratic Nat'l Committee, 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00073 (Box 43)
  - Democrats, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00074 (Box 43)
  - Democrats, 1989; MS074.002.043.00075 (Box 43)
  - Democrats, 1996; MS074.002.043.00076 (Box 43)
  - Democrats and the right, 1993; MS074.002.043.00077 (Box 43)
  - Democrats for Life (Texas), 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00078 (Box 43)
  - Arthur S. DeMoss Foundation, 1992; MS074.002.043.00079 (Box 43)
  - Dennis, Poppy DeMarco, MS074.002.043.00080 (Box 43)
  - Deprogrammer, 1995; MS074.002.043.00081 (Box 43)
  - Dershowitz, Alan, 1985 -- 1992; MS074.002.043.00082 (Box 43)
  - Desmond, Leslie, 1986 -- 1989; MS074.002.043.00083 (Box 43)
  - Des Rochers, Diane, 1992; MS074.002.043.00084 (Box 43)
  - Dettlinger, Chet, 1990; MS074.002.043.00085 (Box 43)
  - DeVries, Edna, 1986 -- 1988; MS074.002.043.00086 (Box 43)
  - Diamond, Sara, 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00087 (Box 43)
  - Dickson, 1988; MS074.002.043.00088 (Box 43)
  - Digital Queers, 1994; MS074.002.043.00089 (Box 43)
  - Direct mail, 1994; MS074.002.043.00090 (Box 43)
  - Discrimination, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.002.043.00091 (Box 43)
  - DC, District of Columbia, 1994; MS074.002.043.00092 (Box 43)
  - Diversity, 1996; MS074.002.043.00093 (Box 43)
  - Divine healing, MS074.002.043.00094 (Box 43)
  - Divorce, 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00095 (Box 43)
  - Dobson, Dr. James, 1986 -- 1996; MS074.002.043.00096 (Box 43)
  - Dodge Bonnie - Born again joke book, 1987; MS074.002.043.00097 (Box 43)
  - Doerr, Edd ARL [1 of 2], 1986 -- 1995; MS074.002.043.00098 (Box 43)
  - Doerr, Edd ARL [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1988; MS074.002.043.00099 (Box 43)
  - Dole, Sen. Robert and Elizabeth, 1987 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - DOMA, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00002 (Box 44)
    Defense of Marriage Act
  - Domestic Partner Coverage - Ins., MS074.002.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Dominos, 1989; MS074.002.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - Donner, Frank, 1986; MS074.002.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Door of Faith Television Network, 1995; MS074.002.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - Doppler, Janice, MS074.002.044.00007 (Box 44)
  - Dornan, Congressman Bob, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00008 (Box 44)
  - The Dove Foundation, 1992; MS074.002.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - Dove, 1993; MS074.002.044.00010 (Box 44)
  - D'Souza, Dinesh, 1995; MS074.002.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - Dukakis, 1988; MS074.002.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - Duke, Charles, Colorado State senator, 1995; MS074.002.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - Duke, Charles, 1996; MS074.002.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - Duke, David, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.044.00015 (Box 44)
  - Dutton, George, 1992; MS074.002.044.00016 (Box 44)
  - Dye, Alan P., 1996; MS074.002.044.00017 (Box 44)
  - Eagle Forum, 1986 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00018 (Box 44)
  - Easterling, Thomas Grayson III, 1993; MS074.002.044.00019 (Box 44)
  - Eckerd, Jack, 1988; MS074.002.044.00020 (Box 44)
  - Ecumenical, 1987; MS074.002.044.00021 (Box 44)
  - Education Alliance, 1996; MS074.002.044.00022 (Box 44)
  - Education - general, 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - Ed USA - Education Under Scrutiny in America, 1994; MS074.002.044.00024 (Box 44)
  - EIDOS - Tatenbaum, Brenda, 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.044.00025 (Box 44)
  - Eisenhower, David, 1985; MS074.002.044.00026 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1986; MS074.002.044.00027 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.044.00028 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.044.00029 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00030 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1996; MS074.002.044.00031 (Box 44)
  - Election, 1984; MS074.002.044.00032 (Box 44)
  - Eliason, Rev. Vic, 1990; MS074.002.044.00033 (Box 44)
  - Elim Fellowship, 1988 -- 1990; MS074.002.044.00034 (Box 44)
  - Emily's List, 1994; MS074.002.044.00035 (Box 44)
  - End Times, 1986 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00036 (Box 44)
  - Environment/environmentalists, 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00037 (Box 44)
  - Enyart, Bob, 1996; MS074.002.044.00038 (Box 44)
  - EEOC, 1994; MS074.002.044.00039 (Box 44)
  - Equal Access Act, 1996; MS074.002.044.00040 (Box 44)
  - Equal Protection Campaign, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.044.00041 (Box 44)
  - Equal Rights Amendments, 1986 -- 1992; MS074.002.044.00042 (Box 44)
  - ERIS Society, 1993; MS074.002.044.00043 (Box 44)
  - ESTEEM, MS074.002.044.00044 (Box 44)
  - Ethical culture, 1986 -- 1990; MS074.002.044.00045 (Box 44)
  - Ethics, 1988; MS074.002.044.00046 (Box 44)
  - Euthanasia, 1995; MS074.002.044.00047 (Box 44)
  - Evangelical Council for Financial Accountability, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.044.00048 (Box 44)
  - Evangelical Press Association (list), 1995; MS074.002.044.00049 (Box 44)
  - Evangelicals, 1987 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00050 (Box 44)
  - Evangelists - general file, 1993; MS074.002.044.00051 (Box 44)
  - Evans, Skip, 1992; MS074.002.044.00052 (Box 44)
  - Evolution, 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.044.00053 (Box 44)
  - Exodus International, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00054 (Box 44)
  - Ewing, Rev. Gene, 1996; MS074.002.044.00055 (Box 44)
  - Exorcism, 1987 -- 1991; MS074.002.044.00056 (Box 44)
  - Eye, Mae, 1993; MS074.002.044.00057 (Box 44)
  - Facts for Action, 1993; MS074.002.044.00058 (Box 44)
  - Fahringer, Catherine, 1994; MS074.002.044.00059 (Box 44)
  - F.A.I.R. Fairness & Accuracy in Reporting, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00060 (Box 44)
  - F.A.I.R. (For Accountability in Religion), 1990; MS074.002.044.00061 (Box 44)
  - Fairness in the Media (vs CBS), 1987 -- 1989; MS074.002.044.00062 (Box 44)
  - Faith healing, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00063 (Box 44)
  - Falling, Billy, 1994; MS074.002.044.00064 (Box 44)
  - Falwell, Jerry, 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00065 (Box 44)
  - Family Education Institute, 1992; MS074.002.044.00066 (Box 44)
  - Family First, 1990; MS074.002.044.00067 (Box 44)
  - Family Forum, 1982 -- 1988; MS074.002.044.00068 (Box 44)
  - Family friendly libraries, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00069 (Box 44)
  - Family planning - legal issues, 1988; MS074.002.044.00070 (Box 44)
  - Family Planning Advocates, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00071 (Box 44)
  - Family planning advocates of NY, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00072 (Box 44)
  - Family planning - Texas, 1993; MS074.002.044.00073 (Box 44)
  - Family planning, W. Mass., 1986 -- 1992; MS074.002.044.00074 (Box 44)
  - The Family - U.S. Gov't Report, 1986; MS074.002.044.00075 (Box 44)
  - Family Research Council [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00076 (Box 44)
  - Family Research Council [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1995; MS074.002.044.00077 (Box 44)
  - Family Research Institute, 1994; MS074.002.044.00078 (Box 44)
  - Bauer, Gary L., 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00079 (Box 44)
  - Family Research Council [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00080 (Box 44)
  - Family Research Council [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00081 (Box 44)
  - Family values, 1986; MS074.002.044.00082 (Box 44)
  - Farah, Joseph, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.002.044.00083 (Box 44)
  - Farrakhan, 1988 -- 1996; MS074.002.044.00084 (Box 44)
  - F.C.C., 1986 -- 1997; MS074.002.044.00085 (Box 44)
  - Federal judges, 1986; MS074.002.044.00086 (Box 44)
  - FEC v. CC, Federal Election Commission [1 of 3], 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - FEC v. CC, Federal Election Commission [2 of 3], 1990 -- 1992; MS074.002.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - FEC v. CC, Federal Election Commission [3 of 3], 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - FEC - Complaint against Swaggart, 1986; MS074.002.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - Federalist Society (a group of conservative lawyers), 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - Feldstein, Richard, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - Fellendorf, George, MS074.002.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - Feminists, 1994; MS074.002.045.00008 (Box 45)
  - Feminists for Free Expression, 1994; MS074.002.045.00009 (Box 45)
  - Feminist Women's Health Centers, 1994; MS074.002.045.00010 (Box 45)
  - Fenn, Peter, 1994; MS074.002.045.00011 (Box 45)
  - Field, Ted, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00012 (Box 45)
  - Fight the Right, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00013 (Box 45)
  - Film code, 1992; MS074.002.045.00014 (Box 45)
  - Films for Christ, 1988 -- 1990; MS074.002.045.00015 (Box 45)
  - Fireovid, Robert, 1992; MS074.002.045.00016 (Box 45)
  - First Amendment rights, 1985 -- 1997; MS074.002.045.00017 (Box 45)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 1996; MS074.002.045.00018 (Box 45)
  - Fischer Foundation, 1988; MS074.002.045.00019 (Box 45)
  - Flag, American, 1989; MS074.002.045.00020 (Box 45)
  - Flag project, 1989; MS074.002.045.00021 (Box 45)
  - Fleming, Mike Newsday, 1988 -- 1989; MS074.002.045.00022 (Box 45)
  - Florida, 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00023 (Box 45)
  - Flouridation, 1984 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00024 (Box 45)
  - Flow charts of the religious right, 1992; MS074.002.045.00025 (Box 45)
  - Tom Flynn CFI, 1991; MS074.002.045.00026 (Box 45)
  - Flynt, Larry, 1985 -- 1997; MS074.002.045.00027 (Box 45)
  - Focus, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00028 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family - Brochures, etc. for 3/95 atty's conference [1 of 5], 1981 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00029 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family - Brochures, etc. for 3/95 atty's conference [2 of 5], 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00030 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family - Brochures, etc. for 3/95 atty's conference [3 of 5], 1981 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00031 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family - Brochures, etc. for 3/95 atty's conference [4 of 5], 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00032 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family - Brochures, etc. for 3/95 atty's conference [5 of 5], 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00033 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family (articles by and about) [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.045.00034 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family (articles by & about) [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00035 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family monthly newsletters [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00036 (Box 45)
  - Focus on the Family monthly newsletters [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00037 (Box 45)
  - FOF (Focus on the Family) fact sheet, 1993; MS074.002.045.00038 (Box 45)
  - FOF Attorney's Conference, 1903 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00039 (Box 45)
    3/1-3/5/95
  - Forced Exposure, 1987; MS074.002.045.00040 (Box 45)
  - Forecast, The, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.045.00041 (Box 45)
  - Foreign, 1988; MS074.002.045.00042 (Box 45)
  - Foster care, 1988; MS074.002.045.00043 (Box 45)
  - Foster, David, AP, 1992; MS074.002.045.00044 (Box 45)
  - Foster, Henry W., Jr., 1995; MS074.002.045.00045 (Box 45)
  - Foster, Marshall, MS074.002.045.00046 (Box 45)
  - Founding fathers, 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.045.00047 (Box 45)
  - Fraad, Lewis MD - Bronx NY, 1986 -- 1990; MS074.002.045.00048 (Box 45)
  - Frankovic, Kathleen A., 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00049 (Box 45)
  - Frasca, Kathy, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.045.00050 (Box 45)
  - FCF fact sheet, 1993; MS074.002.045.00051 (Box 45)
  - Free Congress Foundation, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00052 (Box 45)
  - Free Expression Network, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.045.00053 (Box 45)
  - Free Inquiry, 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.045.00054 (Box 45)
  - Free Inquiry, 1987 -- 1991; MS074.002.045.00055 (Box 45)
  - Free Inquiry articles [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.045.00056 (Box 45)
  - Free Inquiry articles [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00057 (Box 45)
  - Free Press Network/Association, 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.045.00058 (Box 45)
  - Free speech, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00059 (Box 45)
  - Freedom Council Foundation, MS074.002.045.00060 (Box 45)
  - Freedom First, 1989; MS074.002.045.00061 (Box 45)
  - Freedom Forum, 1991 -- 1993; MS074.002.045.00062 (Box 45)
  - Freedom Foundation, 1995; MS074.002.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Freedom from Religion, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - Freedom Monitor, Moderate Voters Project Colorado, 1993; MS074.002.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - Freedom of Choice Act, 1992; MS074.002.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - Freedom of expression, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - Freedom of information, 1985; MS074.002.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - Freedom of religion, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - Freedom to learn, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - Freedom to Read Foundation News, 1991; MS074.002.046.00009 (Box 46)
  - Freedom Village, MS074.002.046.00010 (Box 46)
  - Freedom Writer (Zlotlow copies), 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00011 (Box 46)
    Contains issues not available in IFAS publications (series I); duplicate copies were culled
  - Freethought Observer, 1995; MS074.002.046.00012 (Box 46)
  - Freethought Society, 1994; MS074.002.046.00013 (Box 46)
  - Full Gospel Businessmen, 1987 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - Fund for a Feminist Majority, 1993; MS074.002.046.00015 (Box 46)
  - Fundamentalists, 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.046.00016 (Box 46)
  - Fundamental Presbyterian Publications, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - Fundamentalists Anon, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00018 (Box 46)
  - Fund-raising, 1988; MS074.002.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - Fundraising letters, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.046.00020 (Box 46)
  - Future of Freedom Foundation, 1995; MS074.002.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - Gabler, Mel, 1982 -- 1986; MS074.002.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - Gambling, 1996; MS074.002.046.00023 (Box 46)
  - Gay & lesbian Americans, 1993; MS074.002.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - Gay marriages, 1996; MS074.002.046.00025 (Box 46)
  - Gay Rights, 1996; MS074.002.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - Genesis 2000, 1988 -- 1993; MS074.002.046.00027 (Box 46)